Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America: Records of Locals WAG.234
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Records of TWU Local 100 (New York City), 1931-1978.
  - Publicity, 1937-1939 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Publicity, 1940-1942 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Publicity, 1944 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Publicity, 1945 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Publicity, 1946-1947 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Publicity, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, 1949-1950 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 1950-1952 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Publicity, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Publicity, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Publicity, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Publicity, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Publicity, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Publicity, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Publicity, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Publicity, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Publicity, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Publicity, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Publicity, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Publicity, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Publicity, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Publicity, 1968-1974 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1938-1941 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1946 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Publicity: Clippings, Jan 1948 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Publicity: Clippings, Apr 1948 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Publicity: Clippings, May 1948 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Publicity: Clippings, Jun 1948 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1952 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1955 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Publicity: Clippings, Mar 1962 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1964-1966 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1969, 1971, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1938 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1941 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1942-1943 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1945-1946 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1948-1949 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1950-1952 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1956-1957 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Publicity: Press Releases, 1958-1968 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Publicity: News Releases, 1967-1972 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Publicity: TV and Radio, 1942-1949 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Publicity: TV and Radio, 1950-1951 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Publicity: TV and Radio, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Publicity: TV and Radio, 1954-1957 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Publicity: TV and Radio, 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Publicity: TV and Radio, 1962-1970, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Publicity: Miner Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Publicity: Miner Reports, 1954-1964 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Series II: Records of Other TWU Locals, 1937-1977.
  - Local 1 (Akron, OH), 1937 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Local 1, 1938-1939 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Local 1, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Local 1, 1941 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Local 1, Jan 1942-May 1942 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Local 1, Jun 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Local 1, 1943 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Local 1, 1944 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Local 1, 1945 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Local 1, 1946-1948 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Local 1, 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Local 1, 1951-1952 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Local 1, 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Local 1, 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Local 1, 1960-1963 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Local 1, 1964-1966 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Local 1, 1967-1968 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Local 1, 1969-1973 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Local 1: Agreements, 1937-1944 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Local 1 (Akron, OH), 1968-1970 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Local 1: Agreements, 1945, 1946 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Local 1: Agreements, 1947-1951 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Local 1: Agreements, 1952-1954, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Local 1: Agreements, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Local 101 (Brooklyn, NY), 1938-1941 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Local 101, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Local 101, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Local 101, 1944-1947 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Local 101, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Local 101, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Local 101, 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Local 101, 1952-1953 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Local 101, 1954-1957 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Local 101, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Local 101, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Local 101, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Local 101, Jan 1961-Mar 1961 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Local 101, Apr 1961 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Local 101, May 1961 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Local 101, Jun 1961-Jul 1961 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Local 101, Aug 1961-Dec 1961 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Local 101, 1962-1964 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Local 101, 1965-1968 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Local 101, 1969-1972 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Local 101, 1973-1975 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Local 101: Agreements: 1942; 1943; 1944; 1962; 1963, 1942-1944, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Local 101: Agreements: 1942; 1943; 1944; 1948; 1954; 1961; 1962; 1963, 19421963 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Local 102 (Far Rockaway, NY), 1944-1947 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Local 102: Agreements, 1945 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Local 112 (??, NY), 1937 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Local 150 (New York City, NY), 1940-1947 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Local 150: Agreements, 1945 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Local 151 (Cleveland, OH), 1938 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Local 152 (Detroit, MI), 1937-1940 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Local 153 (Mahanoy City, PA), 1937-1943 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Local 153, 1944-1959 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Local 153: Agreements, 1937, 1941-1951 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Local 155 (Pittsburgh, PA), 1937-1941 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Local 156 (Los Angeles, CA), 1937-1940 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Local 156, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Local 156 (I), 1941 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Local 156 (II), 1941 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Local 156, 1942-1943 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Local 156 (Pasadena, CA);(rechartered, 1946), 1946-1953 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Local 156: Agreements, 1941, 1942 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Local 156: Agreements: 1945; 1946; 1947; 1948; 1950, 1945-1950, 1946, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Local 157 (Harlan, Kentucky), 1937, 1939 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Local 158 (Dayton, Ohio), 1941 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Local 159 (Schenectady, NY), 1937-1938 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Local 159, 1939 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Local 159, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Local 159, 1941 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Local 159, 1942 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Local 159, 1943-1944 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Local 159, 1945-1949 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Local 159, 1950-1957 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Local 159: Agreements: 1938; 1941; 1943; 1945; 1947; 1948; 1949; 1950; 1952, 1938-1952 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Local 160 (Norfolk, VA), 1938-1942 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Local 161 (Philadelphia, PA), 1930-1937 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Local 161, Jan 1938-Jul 1938 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Local 161, Aug 1938-Dec 1938 (Box 71, Folder 8a)
  - Local 161, 1939-1940 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Local 161, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Local 161, 1942-1945 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Local 161: Agreements, 1941, 1943 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Local 162 (Buffalo, NY), 1937 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Local 162, Jan 1938-Apr 1938 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Local 162, May 1938-Dec 1938 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Local 162, 1939 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Local 162, 1940-1944 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Local 162, 1945 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Local 162, 1946 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Local 162: Agreements, 1938 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Local 163 (Norfolk, VA), 1937-1939 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Local 163, 1940-1941 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Local 163, 1942 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Local 163: Agreements, 1940 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Local 164 (Easton, PA), 1937-1945 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Local 165 (Richards, VA), 1937-1940 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Local 166 (Everts, KY), 1937-1939 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Local 166, 1940-1942 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Local 167 (Detroit, MI), 1949 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Local 168 (Sandusky, OH), 1937-1943 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Local 169 (Cumberland, MD), 1938-1942 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Local 170 (Flint, MI), 1937-1939 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Local 170, 1940 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Local 170, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Local 170, 1942-1944 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Local 170, 1945-1949 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Local 170, 1950-1955 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Local 170, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Local 170, 1960-1973 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Local 170: Agreements, 1937, 1938, 1940 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Local 170: Agreements, 1959, 1961, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Local 171 (Corpus Christi, TX), 1937-1939 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Local 171, 1940-1941 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Local 171, 1942-1943 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Local 171, 1944-1949 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Local 171, 1950-1954 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Local 171, 1955-1965 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Local 171: Agreements: 1942; 1944; 1946; 1947; 1948; 1950; 1951; 1952; 1953; 1954; 1961; 1962; 1963; 1964, 1942-1964 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Local 172 (Juneau, AK), 1937-1939 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Local 172, 1940-1945 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Local 173 (Lewiston, PA)Local 173: Agreements, 1938-1940 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Local 174 (Greensboro, NC), 1937-1938 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Local 175 (Baltimore, MD), 1937-1943 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Local 176 (Louisville, KY), 1938-1939 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Local 176, Jan 1940-Jul 1940 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Local 176, Aug 1940-Dec 1940 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Local 176, 1941-1942 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Local 176, 1944 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Local 176, 1945 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Local 176, 1946-1947 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Local 176, 1948-1949 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Local 176, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Local 176, 1951-1952 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Local 176: Agreements, 1944, 1945, 1946 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Local 176: Media Clippings, 1940-1949 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Local 177 (Ketchikon, AK), 1938-1943 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Local 178 (Omaha, NE) [charter recalled] (see also - Locals 223, 228), 1938 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Local 179 (Newark, NJ), 1940 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Local 180 (Philadelphia, PA)Local 180, 1938-1939, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Local 181 (Hazleton, PA), 1941-1944 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Local 181, 1945-1967 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Local 181: Agreements: 1943; 1945; 1947; 1952; 1953; 1954; 1955; 1956; 1958; 1959; 1961, 1943-1961 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Local 182 (Boston, MA), 1938-1945 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Local 182, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Local 183 (Alliance, OH), 1939-1945 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Local 183, 1946-1953 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Local 183, 1955-1971 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Local 183: Agreements: 1939; 1942; 1943; 1944; 1945; 1946; 1947; 1948; 1950; 1952; 1959; 1961; 1962; 1963, 1939-1963 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Local 184 (Cambridge, MA), 1939-1940 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Local 186 (White Plains, NY), 1940 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Local 187 (Charleston, WV), 1940-1943 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Local 188 (Stockton, CA), 1937-1942 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Local 189 (St. Charles, VA), 1940-1941 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Local 190 (Fort Smith, AR), 1937-1942 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Local 190: Agreements, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Local 191 (Williamson, WV), 1940 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Local 192 (Iron Mountain, MI), 1940 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Local 193 (Muncie, IN), 1940 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Local 195 (Huntington, WV), 1940-1941 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Local 196 (Hazard, KY), 1940-1941 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Local 197 (New Kensington, PA), 1940-1958 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Local 197: Agreements: 1941; 1942; 1944; 1956, 1941-1956 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Local 198 (Fall River, MA), 1940-1942 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Local 199 (Honolulu, HA), 1937-1946 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Local 200 (Huntington, WV), 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Local 201 (Chicago, IL), Jan 1940-Sep 1940 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Local 201, Oct 1940-Dec 1940 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Local 201, 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Local 202 (Huntington, WV), 1940-1943 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Local 203 (Charleston, WV), 1941-1945 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Local 204 (Huntington, WV), 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Local 205 (Richmond, VA), 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Local 206 (New Orleans, LA): "History of 1902 Streetcar Strike," (Typescript), undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Local 206, Jan 1941-Apr 1941 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Local 206, May 1941-Sep 1941 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Local 206, Oct 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Local 206, Jan 1942-May 1942 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Local 206, Jun 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Local 206, Jan 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Local 206, Jul 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Local 206, Jan 1944-Jun 1944 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Local 206, Jul 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Local 206, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Local 206, 1946 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Local 206, 1947 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Local 206, 1948 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Local 206, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Local 206, Jun 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Local 206, 1950 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Local 206, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Local 206, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Local 206, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Local 206, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Local 206, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Local 206, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Local 206, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Local 206, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Local 206, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Local 206, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Local 206, 1961-1965 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Local 206, 1966-1973 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Local 206: Agreements, 1941-1946 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Local 206: Agreements, 1947, 1948, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Local 206: Agreements: 1950; 1951; 1952; 1953, 1950-1953 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Local 206: Agreements, 1954-1966 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Local 206: Agreements, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Local 206: Newspaper Clippings, 1941-1956 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Local 206: Press Releases, 1938-1962 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Local 207 (Bessemer, AL), 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Local 208 (Columbus, OH), 1937-1941 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Local 208, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Local 208, 1943 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Local 208, 1944-1945 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Local 208, 1946-1949 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Local 208, 1950-1951 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Local 208, 1952-1956 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Local 208, 1957-1960 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Local 208, 1961-1973 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Local 208: Agreements, 1941-1949 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Local 208: Agreements, 1950-1953 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Local 208: Agreements, 1961-1969 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Local 209 (Audubon, NJ), 1941 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Local 210 (Wilmington, DE), 1961-1969 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Local 210: Agreements, 1961, 1963, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Local 211 (Scranton, PA), 1940-1942 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Title (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_7693ea9c1c8de37aadd38abbd2919d24)
  - Local 212 (Chester, PA), 1940-1945 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Local 212, 1947-1957 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Local 212, 1960-1966 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Local 212: Agreements, 1941-1946, 1959, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Local 213 (Canton, OH), 1940-1942 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Local 214 (Pikesville, KY), 1940-1943 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Local 214, 1944-1946 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Local 214: Agreements, 1942, 1946 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Local 215 (Salt Lake City, UT), 1940-1945 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Local 215: Agreements, 1941-1944 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Local 216 (Lorain, OH), 1941-1942 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Local 218 (Wichita, KA), 1941-1942 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Local 219 (Johnstown, PA), 1941-1944 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Local 220 (Fairfield, AL), 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Local 220: Contracts, 1941 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Local 221 (Aliquippa, PA), 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Local 221, 1944-1950 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Local 221, 1951-1959 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Local 221, 1960-1971 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Local 221: Agreements, 1947-1954, 1960, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Local 222 (Marion, OH), 1941-1946 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Local 222, 1947-1956 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Local 222: Agreements: 1941-1947; 1951; 1952; 1955, 1941-1955 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Local 223 (Omaha, NB), 1941 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Local 223, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Local 223, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Local 223/228, 1944-1945 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Local 223, 1946-1949 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Local 223, 1950-1955 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Local 223/228, 1956-1959 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Local 223, 1960-1973 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Local 223: Agreements, 1941-1949 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Local 223: Agreements, 1952-1954 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Local 223: Agreements, 1959-1972 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Local 223: Clippings, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Local 224 (Texas City, TX), 1941-1948 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Local 225 (Paterson, NJ), 1941-1944 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Local 225, 1945-1950 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Local 225, 1951-1962 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Local 225, 1963-1968 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Local 225, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Local 225, 1971-1975 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Local 225: Agreements, 1942-1945 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Local 225: Agreements, 1946-1948 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Local 225: Agreements, 1949-1952 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Local 225: Agreements, 1953-1955 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Local 225: Agreements, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Local 225: Agreements, 1964-1967 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Local 225: Agreements, 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Local 226 (Boston, MA), 1939-1941 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Local 226, 1942-1943 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Local 226: Agreements, 1942 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Local 227 (Middlesboro, KY), 1941-1942 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Local 228 (Omaha, NB), 1942 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Local 228, 1943 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Local 228 (for additional corresp., see under Local 223, see also Local 178), 1944-1949 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Local 228, 1950-1971 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Local 228, 1942-1952, 1964-1969 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Local 229 (Wellston, OH), 1942-1943 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Local 230 (Chicago, IL), 1942 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Local 230, 1943 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Local 230, 1944 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Local 230, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Local 231 (Albany, NY), 1940-1943 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Local 232 (Topeka, KS), 1942-1944 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Local 233 (Rockingham, NC), 1943, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Local 234 (Philadelphia, PA), undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Local 234, Jan 1943-Jul 1943 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Local 234, Aug 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Local 234, Jan 1944-Feb 1944 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Local 234, Mar 1944-May 1944 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Local 234, Jun 1944-Aug 1944 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Local 234, Sep 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Local 234, 1945 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Local 234, 1946 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Local 234, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Local 234, Jan 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Local 234, Jul 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Local 234, Jan 1949-Feb 1949 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Local 234, Feb 11, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Local 234, Feb 12, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Local 234, Feb 14, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Local 234, Feb 15, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Local 234, Feb 16, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Local 234, Feb 17, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Local 234, Feb 18, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Local 234, Feb 19, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Local 234, Feb 1949 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Local 234, Mar 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Local 234, Jan 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Local 234, Jul 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Local 234, Jan 1951-Jul 1951 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Local 234, Aug 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Local 234, Jan 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Local 234, Jul 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Local 234, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Local 234, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Local 234, 1955 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Local 234, Jan 1956-Jun 1956 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Local 234, Jul 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Local 234, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Local 234 [O'Rourke/Donelly Hearing], Oct 1957 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Local 234, Jan 1958-Jun 1958 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Local 234, Jul 1958-Sep 1958 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Local 234, Oct 1958-Dec 1958 (Box 83, Folder 4a)
  - Local 234, Jan 1959-Mar 1959 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Local 234, Apr 1959-Jun 1959 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Local 234, Jul 1959-Sep 1959 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Local 234, Oct 1959-Dec 1959 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Local 234, Jan 1960-Mar 1960 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Local 234, Apr 1960-Aug 1960 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Local 234, Sep 1960-Dec 1960 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Local 234, Jan 1961-Apr 1961 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Local 234, May 1961-Jun 1961 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Local 234, Jul 1961-Dec 1961 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Local 234, Jan 1962-Jul 1962 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Local 234, Aug 1962-Oct 1962 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Local 234, Nov 1962-Dec 1962 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Local 234, Jan 1963 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Local 234, Feb 1963-Jun 1963 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Local 234, Jul 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Local 234, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Local 234, Jan 1965-Jun 1965 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Local 234, Jul 1965-Dec 1965 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Local 234, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Local 234, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Local 234, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Local 234, Jan 1971-Mar 1971 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Local 234, Apr 19711972 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Local 234, Jan 1973-Feb 1973 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Local 234, Mar 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Local 234, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Local 234, Jan 1975 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Local 234, Feb 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Local 234, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Local 234, Jan 1977-Feb 1977 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Local 234, Mar 1977, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1943 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1944 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1945 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1945, 1946 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1947-1949 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1953, 1957, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1962-1969 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Local 234: Agreements, 1970-1975 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Local 234: Bylaws, 1947-1962 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - L100 234: Fact Finding Board, Jan 16, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Local 234: Fact Finding Board, Jan 17, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Local 234: Fact Finding Board, Jan 18, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Local 234: Fact Finding Board, Jan 20, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Local 234: Fact Finding Board, Jan 21, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Local 234: Fact Finding Board, Jan 23, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Local 234: Minutes of General Membership Meetings, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Local 234: Records of Time Lost for Organizing, 1943-1944 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Local 234: Clippings, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 3)